We've started, we've started that channel.
Applause.
What are we doing today?
We're going to be visiting the home of a male comedian.
We're going to visit a male comedian in his home.
Yes, sir.
He is a bachelor.
I'd like to find out what he likes and what he doesn't like about his house.
I'd be so scared to be evaluated by me.
What about ping pong?
Where's the ping pong?
Why not? Why not?
Don't do this.
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
It's our fault!
It's my fault we're dead!
I've never had a heavy door in my house before.
My own house!
What's wrong?
I'm thirsty.
What?
What? I mean...
Wait a minute. Um...
Don't go in the living room before I do.
What the hell?
Do you have any water? Water.
Yeah, I got water.
Can I use this?
I'll use it. That's great.
Oh, my God, were you guys dating?
Were you guys dating?
You were going out with him?
I got it. Hey, were we dating? Were you guys dating? You were dating?
Yeah, I got it! Yeah?
Nonononononononononononononononononononononononononononononononon?
Important jajaan, hehe
It's only been two minutes since we started, and I've had about six uncomfortable moments But today, we're exploring Morita san's room, Morita san's room, this is Sampo, there's no point in giving a lecture to a guy like this, you don't have to answer it
We're going to explore Morita san's room
Let's visit a room
Morita san, since you're single, I'll give you my evaluation
Evaluation?
What kind of house is it?
I'll see how much he plays with women.
I'm not a bagpiper, so let's see if you're playing with the ladies.
I'm not playing with women that much.
I was hoping you could give me some basic information.
Basic information? What?
Floor plan, address...
That's absolutely terrible.
She's a celebrity, for Christ's sake.
I don't care if it's just a floor plan.
It's not a floor plan.
It's a two-bedroom.
A two-bedroom is pretty nice, isn't it?
It's not for a single person.
It's okay.
For a single person, it's okay.
I'm in.
What's that?
Wood?
It's made of wood.
It's DIY.
It looks like an animal.
What are you talking about?
Who is this dangerous guy? He looks like an animal.
Like a squirrel.
Like Tom Sawyer's house.
He lives in a tree.
I like trees.
What is this guy?
It's wonderful.
You don't think it's great.
That was a really good point.
Honma?
You do DIY?
DIY, the DIY stuff.
Yes, yes, yes. By myself.
The kind I like.
Wooden structure, I mean.
I wanted to live in a wooden room.
That's amazing.
You're making fun of me.
You were saying something like "good points".
That's definitely not true!
I liked it a lot yesterday.
Well, sometimes people say it looks like Tori nobility.
But my favorite kind of room is also wood.
You're lying!
It's true.
Then why do you laugh like an idiot?
I thought it was really nice to make fun of you.
But your face matches my face.
I don't know what to do.
What then?
The squirrel.
The squirrel...
It's like, "Oh, my God!
It's amazing!
Can I watch it for a while?
Where should I start?
No, no, no, I don't want you to look
For you...
Buy some slippers.
And borrow her slippers.
Are you sure you want me to show you everything?
Yes, you can.
It's DIY.
I have a pair of slippers right here.
You're lying.
You guys have great taste.
Is he after you?
He's after me.
I have this one, I bought it in Fukuoka. What? - Is he after you? No, I'm not! Are you after it?
You're kidding me?
You bought this in Fukuoka?
You should get these at the grocery store.
Nice shoes.
These are the staff's.
Most of these are from the staff.
They don't break on the outside, but...
These are great shoes, and these are cute, too.
Stuff.
Are these the staff's? Are these yours?
He looks pissed.
What the hell is wrong with him?
Are we done here?
Look inside... at this door.
Oh, my God.
That's a lot of shoes.
I love sneakers.
And they're clean.
They're so neatly arranged.
You know, for a second there, when I opened it, I thought you were gonna sniff it.
That's definitely not a good idea.
How many shoes?
I like sneakers.
I'm at someone's house.
I said, "You open them.
It's definitely not a good idea.
Eye contact
Out of the corner of my eye.
He pinched my nose.
But there's so many different kinds.
I like a lot of different, well, old-school sneakers.
Wow, a lot of Converse.
There's a lot of Converse.
Why do you like them so much? Since birth.
Since I was born, or rather, since I like the American style.
I bought a lot of American shoes, and this is what I got.
There's more... over here.
This one?
I want to see it right now.
Really?
Don't pick your nose.
There's, like, a whole box of them in here that haven't been worn yet.
Like this.
Yeah. - Yeah.
You don't seem too excited about it.
What?
What's this?
This... is a lot of string.
String.
They're high-cut.
I don't wear them very often.
The reason I say that is because they're a pain in the ass.
It's a pain in the ass.
They're a pain in the ass.
I've got these all rubberized.
What?
You're scaring me.
These are so easy to put on.
This might be good.
It's so convenient.
Hold it like that.
There you go.
That's it.
This is how you put them on.
You don't know what I'm talking about.
I don't know.
That's why there are so many high-cuts.
That's a lot of high-cuts.
But we also have a lot more in stock.
That's a lot of stock.
Next.
What the fuck is this?
I'm sorry. This way then?
I don't think he wants to be seen with this one.
What are you talking about?
Okay, but it's not that big of a deal.
Wait, isn't that your braces?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You could've just said so.
It's cute.
I thought you liked my misaligned teeth.
I really like it.
I think it makes my teeth look better.
I know, but I used to wear braces.
I used to.
I know.
Are you wearing them?
No, I'm not wearing them now.
I'm beautiful now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm clean.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I prefer to be clean.
People are dirtier.
You're much cleaner now, aren't you?
I got my bottom teeth.
When you called me.
I was like, "Rattle, rattle, rattle.
It's been a year now.
But you kept your front teeth.
Well, well, well, well.
That's a bit of a tool of the trade.
I don't need to tell you that I'm leaving a lot of teeth. - Well, well, well, well. That's a business video.
- I'm a big fan of teeth. - I was a huge dental fan.
- Not a fan of mine? - Not me?
- Not my fan? - I was a fan of Morita's teeth, so I'm a little disappointed.
- Who are you chasing now? - Right now, uh, Iguchi.
- Iguchi. Those two rows? That's okay. - Yes, it's dirty. I like that one.
- What about whitening?
I do whiten my teeth once in a while.
Yeah, but it's Ziva, right?
Ziva, all of it.
Yeah, that's well written.
I don't know, maybe no implants.
Yeah, I don't like it when you say implants.
I'd rather have jivas.
As for the teeth.
He doesn't have a block length of teeth.
I don't know what to do.
It's not like we live in a house or anything.
I'll look.
What about here?
There's some color there.
Lotion.
Makeup remover.
Here.
Definitely.
What's that?
There's a girl.
What is it?
It's a cleansing farm.
I don't know what it is.
I can't open this place.
That's why I didn't notice it.
I didn't even know it was there.
Which one is it?
Which one?
That's a great contact.
I got mine, too.
What are those? They're contacts.
Oh, my God.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who put these down?
I'm a little scared too.
Who's leaving these here?
It's a girl.
Who lives here besides me?
Yes.
There's two of them.
You're trying to move on, aren't you?
The year before last.
I had a girlfriend until the end of the year.
That's her?
What are those contacts for?
These are really natural contacts.
They're color contacts.
But someone left them behind.
That's what I'm thinking.
I don't care if he took a bath or something.
It's a real bachelor mess.
And this place is DIY.
DIY?
There's something I like about you.
I like people who keep things neat and tidy.
I like people who put these things on and keep things neat and tidy.
I like people who put these on and keep things neat and tidy.
It's nice, and so is this.
Yes, yes, yes.
I like people who do that.
Thank you.
You know this?
You really should do this.
What's this?
You're supposed to blow-dry your hair back there.
You dry here, right here, right here, right here.
No, no, no, this is my technique. Look.
Here, right here.
Right here. Then all the hair falls out here.
The hair will definitely fall out. It's a hair dryer.
It's just a little... ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
I don't know...
Well, there is, but...
No, it can't be helped
Don't say "no"!
It can't be helped.
You've fallen so hard.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't keep going on and on about it.
My hair didn't fall out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna finish all my hair over here.
I'm going to complete all my hair over here.
I'm glad we did that.
In the bedroom.
I don't want anyone to see it, but...
Oh, that's cute.
Where's the bed?
This is from a place called Truck Furniture.
There's a furniture store in Osaka that I like.
It's cute.
This is so cool.
It's from there.
This is a book bed... you know, the kind Americans use to read books before bed.
That's what it's for.
Is that right?
The room has a really nice atmosphere.
Is it?
What's this?
It's a handwriting that Yuki Uchida gave me.
I loved Yuki Uchida so much when I was in middle school.
I wrote her name in my notebook.
I liked her so much that I joined the Minchotai.
I told her that I liked her so much that I joined the Civil Affairs Bureau.
Yuki Uchida wrote this on Shabekuri 7.
And I was so happy to receive it.
It's on my pillow.
I'm so happy!
It's the kind of room where a lot of dreams come true after a successful career, isn't it?
It's so-so.
Well, when I say dreams come true...
Don't go there, Akichan.
Why not?
For now.
Why?
Not now.
Is it okay? Hey, Anochan.
Anochan.
Not now.
Doesn't she know...
A box of candy?
Maybe he thinks it's a box of candy or something.
Okamoto Co.
Don't say that
Don't say "manufacturer.
There.
Maybe you shouldn't do that so much.
You-know-who
You-know-who.
You're throwing up a lot.
Um...
I know you don't always read me the right way.
I do a lot of porno shows.
I get, like, tons of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, what's this? I get so many, so many, so many, so many, so many, so many, so many, so many, so many, so many.
What's this?
It's just a little bit of gross stuff.
Where do you use this?
It's for your whole body. It's like a body cream.
It's like a body cream. There's a lot of it.
What's in that?
What's that?
Ha-ha-ha.
You're buying it for yourself.
I get them for free.
I'll get you a refill.
Ha-ha-ha.
We're well-stocked around here.
That's why...
Well... now...
Thank you for bringing it out.
Don't let me out! It's a massager.
There's a lot going on.
What's this?
What's that?
What is it?
Um...
You know, the one Yoko Kumada and her friends used.
Oh, she mentioned something about it.
It's called something like an organizer.
It's stylish. Curtains...
I found some nice ones.
Clothes? Is this a closet?
This is a walk-in.
Wow, it's a walk-in.
Wow. - It's beautiful.
Neat and tidy.
Very neat and tidy.
It's very detailed.
You like it clean? This kind of thing.
Well, I like to keep things organized.
It's like a thrift store.
It is.
Clothes store.
This... this was given to me by Mr. Tokoro.
What's this?
It's so cute!
I heard it costs about a million dollars.
Mr. Tokoro gave it to me the other day.
Can't you wear it?
No, it's okay, but I thought I should wear it.
I'm wearing it.
It makes me nervous.
I really like the same kind of thing.
What? We're the same? We're the same?
We're not the same.
I think we're the same if you're not interested.
I go to thrift stores too.
You're kidding, right?
He's going after you.
Will you stop it?
Why would I go after Bali?
You made it clear.
I've been holding back.
I really like vintage clothes.
You mean you're going to Shimokita and Harajuku?
Shimokita, Harajuku Park, Nakameguro...
I'll be there.
What?
You...
Yes, but!
I go to Nagoya too.
I'll go to Nagoya too.
Gunma...
I go to Kiho and buy a lot of eels.
Oh, what's this?
Matching apps.
Even if you do it, you do it on the same day.
I don't want to do it
I'm doing it on the same day as the person I'm going out with.
We're definitely not each other's type
Morita-chan can't handle a girl like me.
It's true, Jajan's good at what he does
I like Morita's teeth
I fixed her teeth already
This one?
It's no big deal over there
Drying in the room
What's this room?
What's this room for drying clothes?
Is there such a room?
Yeah.
Heh.
Oh, let's go to Ninyara then.
Yeah.
I'm too burnt out to go outside.
Clothes.
That's extravagant.
I mean, you're pretty particular about it.
Well, well, well, well.
I like to take care of my clothes.
I really like clothes. And I like them well, too.
Fashionable.
Fashionable. We don't have that much time here.
No, I don't.
But I still feel like I won't be overtaken by this place.
I like the attention to detail.
Thank you very much.
What's all this?
Is that an electric kickboard?
Are you using it?
No, I don't.
I'm scared. If Morita-san were here, he'd be in town. I'm not sure, but a kickboard? Are you using it? No, I don't use it. I'd be afraid to go to town if I saw Mr. Moreta with one of these.
I have a kickboard, too.
What?
It was outside.
The Speleo? Yeah.
You know, sometimes I ride my kickboard around Gotanda.
I'm on a kickboard.
When you're kickboarding, don't your teeth dry out?
Teeth?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I can't get it.
They don't.
Oh, no? It won't go away? Why don't you just close your mouth? You can't close your mouth. It's not because you don't have enough skin.
I like it when it gets moldy. I like it when your teeth are dry.
You like it when my teeth are dry?
Good point.
It doesn't take a kickboard to do that.
Why not? When it's a shovel.
Good point, where the teeth are dry.
Unique.
Here's another one.
This is another DIY project.
Wow! That's amazing!
You can put this all the way up.
I hate dust on top of the wardrobe.
I made a DIY system to keep all the dust out.
How long does this take? How long does it take to make?
But, I don't know, maybe three days. Maybe this big.
It's okay. I want you to make it.
Shall we make it?
Shakshuka's after me.
No, I'm not. I'm not.
Do it DIY.
No, I'm not going to do it.
Next to wiring the TV, you're doing DIY.
I'm not going to do that.
But I'm totally going to make something, Hanana.
I had a room for clothes, too.
But it turned out to be a mess.
I'm the type of person who does my best, but...
I like it when things get a little dusty.
This is super good.
I made it.
Really? - Yeah.
This is good.
Well, if you're gonna do it, you should really make it official.
I really want you to do it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I thought you were Catan.
No, I'm not.
It's a little embarrassing.
Wow.
It's beautifully done.
Look at that.
I have three of these jerseys.
Really? They're the same, right? I mean, there's three of these West Germany jerseys... and they're all the same.
It's the West German national team jersey that every soccer fan loves.
Three jerseys?
I have three jerseys.
I love jerseys.
Oh, yeah, you do.
What do you want me to do?
That's what I'm supposed to do.
You mean he's going to tell me today?
I love jerseys.
I've always loved jerseys.
It's fun!
All of this.
Let's go in the living room.
Oh, the living room?
I'll go to the living room, too.
I usually do the living room first.
In that order.
Let's start with the living room.
What's this?
This is the pantry, the storage room.
Oh!
Nice house.
Yes, it is.
It's hard to throw away things that people give you, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah...
So you can't just put it aside for now.
I see.
I see
And here's the thing...
Don't put it there.
Anchan.
I've got it.
Yeah.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's like a single adulterer's house
I mean, it's like...
It's like...
Ah! NES.
Oh, my God!
You're not from my generation.
That's a lot of stuff.
I bought a bunch of these when I was a kid.
Growing up.
It happens sometimes.
Like Super Mario... for drinks at home.
Drinking at home?
With girls?
When I'm done with Super Mario.
I'm going to play Exasperity Sigle.
Oh, my God!
With you?
That's disgusting.
Isn't that healthy?
I agree.
Consent is important.
Wait, where'd you get this couch? This is the truck furniture that goes with the bed.
This is really good, right here.
This is so good.
I love it.
Isn't it called "Kuta"?
It does, but it's crumbly.
You're keeping it so clean.
If it gets crumpled up again...
Once it's like this...
Once it's like this, it comes back.
It's a good one.
If you use it more, the crumbs will become a very nice taste.
As a taste?
This chair is expensive, too.
What's this?
That's one too.
It's cute.
But I think it's about 70,000 yen
When Mr. Yoshizumi saw Mr. Morita buying one, he was worried
But I thought they were the same, so I decided not to buy it.
Mr. Yoshizumi, a creator has to sit in a chair like this
What are you doing here? Working?
I work remotely here, or I make stuff
What are you working on here, or remotely, or making stuff, etc., etc., etc., etc.?
I made this, too... this resin table... and this... this is what I like...
I can't put it in, even if I do it, I want you to do it. - I want you to do it. This is good. - It's good, isn't it? - I'll put CDs and stickers in it, and I'll also put key chains like this.
- Oh, that's good. It's really good. - It would cost about 200,000 yen if I bought it.
- That's right. - You can only do this by hand, so a resin table is a great idea.
- It's amazing. - Wow. - So, if I really want to make one, I can just tell you and you can make it for me? Well, it depends on how I feel at the time.
It depends on our relationship.
Wow, it's really good!
So stylish!
I like that you don't make it yourself.
Well, you can have this one made for me.
I'd love to have a resin table artist like that.
I'd like to have a resin table made by an artist.
I said, "I want something like this.
I asked him to make it for me on Youtube.
Wow, that's great!
I don't know what this is.
We have one of these at home, too.
Oh my God!
Oh, my God, give me a break!
It's bizarre!
I'll send you a picture.
Oh, my God!
It's just a coincidence that we're together.
It's too weird.
Are you stalking me?
I'm scared, too.
I love nightmares, Fanny.
Nightmares.
It's called EvaFresh.
EvaFresh.
My teeth close up at night.
They're closing up.
That's amazing.
I'm scared.
I know.
How was it?
I think it was fun.
I've never seen anything like it.
The idea of entertaining a girl.
Girls don't really like that.
They get so excited when they see you like this.
I'd have been happy if I had.
The first time I had a drink here.
Like, "Let's go to my house for a drink.
You know, girls who come over and don't show any reaction.
I'm like, "What? I'm like, "What?
No reaction? What about girls who don't react to you? Do you get no reaction from them?
There are people who don't react to me.
First of all, a wooden wall...
They say, "That's a wooden wall.
They're like, "That's a wall of wood.
Most of them are like that.
They just go home.
They'll fail, won't they?
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no.
Out of 100 points.
There's just so much going on...
What's the score?
100 points.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
After all!
Seriously!
No!
It's the Internet news!
Why are you being so creepy! No! No!
I'm serious!
I really enjoyed the room.
I'm a sucker for a tree house, and I'm a sucker for a tree house.
You know, with the trees and Eva's freshness, and the way they take care of their clothes.
I love clothes too.
It's like coming home to my own house.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
And the sofa. I have a green one just like this one.
It's really scary, honestly scary.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
We're both good.
Maybe we can make it.
If you have any questions, just ask, and we'll start there.
It's not too sudden.
I don't think so.
Let's have him do a DIY project on the show next time.
I'd prefer to do it in a day, but I don't mind.
I'd rather do it in a day, but I don't mind. I'd rather do it in a day.
What kind?
Something big... that can't be done in a day.
What kind of things can you do?
I don't know. I can do a shelf.
Oh, a shelf! I want a shelf!
So you want it to look like my house?
Yeah, like this house.
Like this house.
I want to.
What's that? With you? I want to... what's that?
It would be faster if we lived together.
I'll see you next time.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you for watching.